

#### CONTACT



8606123342



midhunmo722@gmai l.com



Ayyappanezhathu, Vaikom P.O - 686141



DOB - 22/07/1996

SKILLS

MS Word, MS Excel



PDI Inspection Diagnosis



Mechnanical Repairing



LANGUA GE S

**ENGLISH** 

\_\_\_

HINDI

ш

MALAYALAM

\_\_\_\_

HOBBIES







# MIDHUN M

3+ Years of professional experience in automobile industry as light vehicle mechanic and PDI technician. Looking for a better position especially in technical section at a good company that can benefit from superb customer service skill and extensive knowledge in automobile technologies.

## **EDUCATION**

Automobile Engineering Diploma

2016-2018

State Board of Technical Education

**Higher Secondary Education** 

2012-2014

Board of Vocational Higher Secondary

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Automobile PDI Technician

2019-present

Premier Honda, Kottayam

A PDI In charge is responsible for managing the overall process of functional and visual inspection of the vehicles before delivery to ensure it meets the customers' expectations. The individual is responsible for ensuring stringent checks/ inspections (including that thorough cleaning and washing) through PDI Supervisor and his team of technicians and washers.

**Automobile Mechanic** 

2018-2019

Leyland Automobiles, Vaikom

General Check-up for light vehicles
Maintenance and repair mechanical works